How is that even possible? The guy was a
seventh grade substitute math teacher
with no college degree and he's managing
the Rothschild family's billions. It
doesn't make any sense. By not releasing
the documents that gives rise to
conspiracies, it eats away at, you know,
trust in your administration and it
leads people to think that, you know
what, they may have something on him.
Maybe that's why he won't release the
documents. Bobby Jr. and his mom pull
into the driveway. He gets out of the
car. He's walking past his dad and he's
looking at his dad and he hears his dad
say to Mone, "Tell me your people didn't
do this." And Mccon says, "I don't know
who did it." I think that Trump really
believed that as soon as we started
hitting the Iranians and we killed not
just Ayatami, but virtually the entire
defense leadership, he really believed
the country would just collapse like a
house of cards. And it didn't. So, we
may have bitten off more than we could
chew here.
>> Hey everyone, welcome to another sitdown
with Michael Francis. Hope everybody is
doing well. All is very good, very
blessed on this end, my friends. As
always, I give all the praise, honor,
glory, and thanksgiving to our God for
that because he deserves it. Okay, I
have an explosive guest today. You might
have heard him before, but I talked to
him, I think, in a different way than
many other people have. Explosive. It
might be the most interesting
conversation I've ever had and I think I
said that once before, but this is
explosive. You got to listen in. Before
I get into it, I want to thank all of
you that have been subscribing in the
past couple of videos. We got a couple
of thousand new subscribers. Why?
Because I asked a favor of all of you.
Uh my birthday's coming up May 27th and
my team has challenged me to get to 2
million subs. We're getting close. very
good possibility we can hit it by May,
but all of you have to uh contribute. If
you like the content, if you don't like
me, don't don't worry about it, you
know. But if you do, please subscribe.
It would be a favor to me. A birthday
present, I should say, for my birthday
on May 27th. I'm going to be 75 years
old, 3/4 of a century. Where did the
time go, people? I got to tell you this.
There was a time I didn't think I'd make
it till 75, but not there yet, but I'm
getting close. So, we'll see. But if you
can do me that favor, please. Birthday
present. Just subscribe. And hey, thank
all of you who have done so already. And
thank you for being loyal followers
because without you, I don't have a
platform. Bottom line, that's it. John
Kiraku,
this is my guest today. ExCIA agent, got
himself in some trouble. He was a
whistleblower many, many years ago while
he was with the agency. He blew the
whistle on a terrorist that might have
had something to do al-Qaeda something
to do with the um bombing of the World
Trade Center way back when. Very, very
possible. We don't know that for a fact,
but very possible. But he blew the
whistle on some agents that were
waterboarding this guy cuz that's an
outlawed practice. You're not allowed to
do it. He ends up getting indicted and
he got some federal time. He went to
prison over it. The funny thing is or
the ironic thing is the guys that
actually did the water boarding, nothing
happened to them. So anyway, he's got a
lot of experience, but I'm telling you,
the information that he's providing is
explosive on Israel. I'll tell you how
explosive it is. Many of you know my
position there. He's got me thinking
about Israel. I have to say that
Epstein, what he's going to tell you
about Epstein, and it makes sense. It
all fits in. It makes sense. the war in
Iran and Israel's involvement. Does
Israel really have something over the
United States and Trump? He's going to
talk about it. You decide. Getting me to
think. The Kennedy assassination. I
found out something today I didn't know.
Do I believe the mob was involved?
Absolutely. Does he break that theory at
all? Absolutely not. Not a theory. It's
a fact. No question about it. But he
gave me even more evidence to prove that
it's so in my mind. Without a doubt. Did
Epstein commit? Hell no. Told you that.
Hell no. And he's going to talk about
that, too. We We talked about a lot of
different things, but all of them fit
and make sense. How Israel is in the
center of a lot of this stuff. I I tell
you what, he's got me thinking. And
people, I want to tell you something. I
don't mind admitting I'm wrong. If I
take a certain position, and there's
evidence to show that, hey, this
position, you better rethink. I'll
rethink it. I have no problem telling
you. None whatsoever. You know, I'm not
invincible. I'm not, you know, beyond
making a mistake or whatever, you know,
based upon information I know. And if
something new comes in and I believe it
to be credible enough to at least give
it some thought, I'm going to say it.
And I'm telling you, I'm rethinking
something about Israel with respect to
Epstein and with respect to the war in
Iran and maybe a few other things. Even
the Kennedy assassination, he said some
things that you're not going to believe.
So, let's explore it. Listen, I have a
lot of Israeli friends, but the truth is
the truth. They have nothing to do with
whatever's going on there with Israel.
That's for sure. But he said some things
John did that really made sense. This
guy, this is an explosive interview. And
you know what? He's credible. I I can
feel it. I can sense it. He's credible.
So, let's uh without any further delay,
my very very special guest, John
Kiryaku. And I hope I'm saying that name
right. I believe I am. John, welcome.
Mike, I have to say I have been a fan of
yours for so long. I think you do such
great and important work and that this
is a real like personal treat for me.
Thank you so much for the invitation.
>> Well, I really I really appreciate that.
I didn't know that you knew me at all,
but uh I appreciate that very much.
Thank you.
>> In fact, you and I were on a panel
together on uh Pierce Morgan.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, that's right. Gosh, Ron, I forgot
about that. That's right. Alan Alan
Dersowitz and Scott Horton went to the
mat and you and I just kind of sat there
like this and just let them kill each
other.
>> Right. That's right. Yeah. We we were
the uh we were the calm ones on that.
Yes.
>> We were the voices of reason.
>> Well, it's great to have you. I I've
been looking forward to this also, John.
>> Thank you so much. That that means a lot
to me.
>> Yeah. But I want to I want to jump right
into this and they'll be editing this
right away because this
>> everybody's mind. Was Jeffrey Epstein a
spy in your opinion or experience I
should say?
>> I I believe pretty firmly that Jeffrey
Epstein was a spy but not in the
traditional sense of of a James Bond
kind of spy. Um I think that he was what
we call an access agent
most likely for Mossad but but it's
deeper than that and I'll explain that
in a second. An access agent is well to
explain an access agent let's say that
you are a foreign intelligence service
and you want information from some of
the most powerful some of the most
important people on earth. You're not
going to recruit Bill Clinton or Bill
Gates or Prince Andrew or or the British
ambassador of the United States. Those
people are not recruitable and they
don't need money. So money is not going
to motivate them. So you hire instead
somebody who has access to those people.
Somebody who can whine them and dine
them, make them comfortable, have them
drop their guard, they speak a little
bit out of school, and then you can
report that back to your handlers.
That's valuable information. When I was
in training, when I was in CIA training,
one of my instructors said something
that has stuck with me for all these
years. He said that the best recruitment
he ever made over a 30-year career was a
copy machine repair man. And we all
laughed.
>> And he said, "Hear me out. We all wish
that we could go overseas and recruit
the prime minister. None of us are going
to recruit the prime minister. But you
recruit a copy machine repair man
knowing that the prime minister's copy
machine is going to go down eventually
or it's going to need to be serviced or
cleaned. And so when that happens, he
goes into the prime minister's office.
Security is there to make sure, you
know, he doesn't steal documents or
whatever. He's not interested in that.
What he does is as he's cleaning and
servicing the copy machine, he's
installing a little device that we
created so that every time somebody
makes a copy on that machine, it
transmits a copy to Langley. That's an
access agent. You haven't recruited the
prime minister, but you did the next
best thing because everything that the
prime minister is seeing, you are now
seeing. I believe that Mossad recruited
Jeffrey Epstein as an access agent
either to collect information from these
very very important people or to plant
the Mossad's point of view on XYZ issue
in the in the minds of these very
important people. Now, in this latest
trunch of the Epstein documents, among
among horrors, we also learned that he
repeatedly reached out to the CIA and
the FBI, asking volunteering
to help them and to do work for them. He
did the same with the British MI5 and
MI6. And he repeatedly attempted to
engage with what was then the KGB, now
the SVR, to get a one-on-one meeting
with Vladimir Putin. The Russians
actually offered him a meeting with
Putin and two national security aids and
he turned it down. He said he needed for
it to be one-on-one with Putin and the
Russians weren't biting. So I think that
this was all about the Mossad and then I
think that he thought maybe he could
freelance a little bit and just see what
else he could come up with.
>> All right, my friends, let me tell you
something and I mean this. You know how
wine is made? The grapes get crushed. It
sits in the dark. It goes through
pressure. Most things don't survive. And
then it becomes something beautiful.
That's my story. That's this wine. If
you're going through something right
now, trust the process and try the wine.
frine.com.
Wow, John, that that is so interesting.
But, you know, it brings up some other
questions. You know, do you think this
happened in the very beginning? Because
a lot of people, myself included, like
where did this guy come from? all of a
sudden it seemed out of nowhere he meets
up with you know Les Wexner and he gives
him the keys to the kingdom for some
reason.
>> Um do you think it started like before
that or once he started to show that he
had money and he had some relationships?
Is that when maybe they started to
recruit him or use him?
>> I I think it may have been before and
and I'll tell you why
now. And I'll preface this by saying
that Les Wexner adamantly denies this,
but I think they may have been lovers.
Jeffrey Epstein was was a junior high
school substitute math teacher with no
college degree.
I would love to own the widest townhouse
in Manhattan. I would love to own my own
island in the Caribbean and my own fleet
of private jets, but I'm a normal
person. Normal people don't just fall
into something like that. We know that
that the origin of his wealth, I won't
say the basis, but the origin of his
wealth was with or from Les Wexner. Less
Wexner being of course the wealthiest
man in the state of Ohio. And
>> Les Wexner latched on to Jeffrey
Epstein, adopted so to speak, Jeffrey
Epstein without any logical reason for
doing so. There had to be 500,000 people
in the United States that would have
been better qualified to manage this
billionaire's money.
Why Jeffrey Epstein? So, I think that
I think that the Israelis directed him
to target Les Wexner. That's what got
him started. Wexner testified a couple
of weeks ago that he was the one that
had um spoken to the Rothschilds and the
Rothschilds said, "Oh, you should talk
to our friend Jeffrey Epstein. He
manages our money." How is that even
possible? The guy was a seventh grade
substitute math teacher with no college
degree and he's managing the Rothschild
family's billions. It doesn't make any
sense. So, I think that this was one of
those very long-term operations.
You know, it's easy to fall into into
sort of a rut where
we compare we as as CIA officers compare
our operations with the operations of
other intelligence services. We have a
very limited timeline in our operations.
You don't get promoted if you don't make
a recruitment. And if you don't make a
recruitment in 6 months or 12 months,
you move on and you move on to the next
guy or the next issue or whatever, the
Israelis, the Russians, the Cubans, they
have a much longer term view where
they'll pluck somebody out of obscurity
like Jeffrey Epstein, and they'll manage
him for 20 years, 30 years, no matter
how long it takes, they know that in the
end, he's going to be able to report to
them.
>> Wow. You know that you you brought up
something interesting. I only learned
about this recently. What do you think
the connection between the Roth trials
because that's like stunning and
Epstein. How did that even come about?
It is completely unexplained in these
documents. So you know this these 3
million documents, Mike, this was like a
tease for the American public. And there
are still between 2.7 million and 3
million more pages that haven't been
released and according to Pam Bondi now
won't be released. But
we we're we're teased with this
information about the Rothschilds
to the point where Congress subpoenas
Les Wexner and he just teases more. In
fact, you may have seen the clip from
his testimony on YouTube where a
congressman asks him a question and he
gives what appears to be an honest
answer and on a hot mic his lawyer leans
in and he says, "I will kill you if next
time you don't answer the question yes
or no."
>> So, they don't want us to know the
details of the of the origins of these
relationships. There's something there
that is embarrassing, that is
humiliating, that is possibly dangerous,
that they just don't want us to know
about. For example,
they talk about beef jerky in something
like 1,500 different emails. Jeffrey is
having the guy over to make the big
jerk, the beef jerky. The guy's coming
over to teach us how to make beef jerky.
We're going to make the beef jerky.
We're going to freeze the beef jerky. I
love beef jerky. They talk about beef
jerky nine ways from Sunday, but you
know what they never talk about? They
never talk about eating beef jerky. And
so
>> what are they actually talking about? Is
it children? Is it people?
>> We don't know. There are more questions
now after the release of these three
million pages than we had before we knew
anything at all.
It's it's John. It's it's unbelievable.
It really is. I mean,
the the extent of this operation that
this guy had over, I guess, a 20-year
period or something that the people that
he was in contact with, you know. So, I
mean, look, I I think everybody believes
and knows if we had to bet our life on
it, there was a huge cover up here. And
I think I I don't know if you Yeah. If
you're aware that Marjorie Taylor Green,
she talked about on a YouTube uh deal
that she had a conversation with Trump.
>> Yes.
>> And Trump actually told her, she said,
you know, why are you so mad at me for
wanting these documents released
unredacted? You're not in them
>> to any any problem with you, you know.
And he said, yeah, but many of my
friends are.
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, that was his response. A and I
think that I think that she was so
courageous
in her willingness to stand up, but it
was too much even for her and they they
forced her all the way out of
Washington. You know, when when you've
got members of of both political
parties, very high ranking members of
both political parties, presidents of
both political parties that are at least
implicated in accusations
Then you have to ask, you know, what
what would we expect them to do other
than to try to cover up? I'll tell you
one thing that that bothers me very much
about these these documents in the
latest trunch.
I have a very particular interest in
John Brennan. John and I kn have known
each other for 30 36 years. John
Brennan, it was always my belief, was a
murderous sociopath.
And what we saw in these latest
documents was
the Obama White House general counsel,
Katherine Remler, who just last week was
asked to resign as the general counsel
for Goldman Sachs. Kathern Remler
sending an email to Jeffrey Epstein
saying, "John Brennan gave me the CIA's
highest honor today." Pretty neat, huh?
Well, I was at the CIA for 15 years. I
know what honor she got. That honor was
reserved for CIA officers who were
killed in the line of duty.
So, what in the world could Katherine
Remler have possibly done to warrant the
CIA's highest honor? An honor that is
that is reserved for the organization's
greatest heroes. And then she tried
repeatedly to get Jeffrey Epstein and
John Brennan together for breakfast or
for lunch. We don't know if she was ever
successful cuz Brennan's not talking.
And if there was a response, it wasn't
released in this latest trunch. But like
I said, there there were so many other
lines of investigation that were
revealed to us
that I'm not sure we could ever get
through it. And everybody's implicated.
>> Was she even an uh a CIA operative in
any way or
>> she was a lawyer?
>> Remler.
>> Nope. She was a lawyer who went directly
into government justice department.
Worked her way up in the Justice
Department and then Obama brought her
over to the White House as uh as White
House counsel. She didn't have any
experience in intelligence at all. But I
have a theory. I follow these issues
very very closely and and forgive me if
I'm a little overly passionate about it.
But
in 2009, I was the chief investigator on
the Senate Foreign Relations Committee
and
a journalist from uh the New Yorker
magazine called me and said that she had
information that John Brennan, who at
the time was the deputy national
security adviser for counterterrorism,
was hosting meetings at the White House
every Tuesday morning at 7:00 called the
Tuesday morning kill list meetings. I
said, "What are you talking about?"
So, she came to my office, closed the
door, we had this off thereord
conversation.
It's on the record now because she
published it. But she said that every
Tuesday morning at 7:00 a.m., John
Brennan chaired a meeting made up of
attorneys from the Justice Department,
the CIA, and the White House, as well as
representatives from the CIA's um uh
special activities division, and they
would come up with a list of people to
kill that week. They would agree on the
list.
>> Wow.
Brennan would sign it on behalf of the
president and then the teams would fan
out around the world, kill everybody
that was on the list and then meet again
the next Tuesday morning for that week's
list of people to kill.
And I think that
she was probably responsible
for White House approval
for all those assassinations.
Now, you can't go to the Washington Post
if you're John Brennan and say, "Hey,
shout out to Katherine Remler. She helps
me kill so many people. I just want to
say what a great patriot she is." You
can't do that.
So, you give her an award that nobody is
supposed to know about. It's a
classified award.
And then she blew the classification by
immediately emailing Jeffrey Epstein and
saying, "John Brennan just gave me the
the top award that the CIA has. It's
sick."
Wow.
>> You know, John, I'm glad you just uh
verified something for me. I always
looked at John Brennan as one of the
most arrogant guys. I just didn't like
anything about him and everything that
I've seen with him. I I likened him. He
was a worse version in my opinion of Jay
Ed Garoover. And I said, "This guy must
have a lot of dirt on a lot of people."
>> Yes, sir.
>> Yeah. I I really believe that. But man,
to hear something like that, an actual
kill list.
>> Oh yeah. An actual kill list. And in the
beginning, Brennan denied denied denied
that any such thing existed.
And then when the magazine found enough
people and it was like a half a dozen
people
sitting, you know, current CIA people
saying, "Of course we have a kill list.
What do you think we do all day long?"
they were able to run with the with the
story and publish it.
>> Crazy.
>> It's just unbelievable.
>> So, John, there is, you know, when I
look back at that statement that Trump
said, many of my friends are involved.
There is some I mean the president has a
lot of power but there has to be people
in this world that in some way control
him or keep him you know quiet to a
certain extent and maybe not only true
of him but others and what I want to ask
you is there's this flood of information
out not information of opinions out
there that it's really Israel that has
so much control over the United States
over our presidents and everything else.
Now, you know, they're all talking that
this is Israel's war with Iran. It's not
ours. What What could you say about
that, John?
>> Well, I could forgive me for smiling. I
could say a couple of things. In all the
years that I was at the CIA,
literally every single time that an
Israeli prime minister would come to
Washington, and usually they come once
or twice a year, sometimes more. In the
last year, Benjamin Netanyahu has come
seven times. Literally, every single
time they would come, no matter who the
prime minister was, no matter who the
American president was, they would ask
us to bomb Iran. Every single time, and
I mean going back to the 80s, and every
single president would say, "I'm not
going to do that. It's going to be the
start of World War II. I'm not going to
do it."
In fact, George HW Bush, the father,
actually revoked
uh loan guarantees for Israeli housing
construction because the Israelis would
not stop with these constant requests to
bomb Iran. We always sort of hoped that
the Iranians would turn around, they
would agree to talks, maybe we would go
through the Omanis, maybe we'd go
through the Algerians, and then
everybody could live happily ever after.
That never happened. But there was this
constant drum beat of pressure from the
Israelis that we've got to bomb Iran.
You got to bomb Iran. Well,
we didn't bomb Iran until Donald Trump.
And I have friends at the White House. I
have friends in the administration and
they all tell me the same thing. They
say that Trump agreed to bomb Iran
because Benjamin Netanyahu threatened
him and told him, "If you don't bomb
Iran, we're going to use nuclear weapons
against Iran." Now, of course, the
Israelis have never admitted that they
have a nuclear program. But analysts
believe that they have between 80 and
200 nuclear warheads. The Israelis are
not signitories to the uh nuclear
non-prololiferation treaty.
Interestingly enough, the Iranians are.
I can also tell you that the deal that
we had with the Iranians that was called
the JCPOA and the deal that the United
Nations had with the Iranians were
identical to the deal that the
International Atomic Energy Agency had
negotiated with Saddam Hussein's Iraq
for for observation of Iraq's uh weapons
programs.
lead seals on every door, cameras
pointing, you know, 360°
spot inspections with no uh with no
warning, no coordination. The Iranians
had agreed to all of that. In addition
to that, in addition to the Iranians
agreeing, the CIA wrote two national
intelligence estimates. This is the
highest level analysis that's produced
by the entire American intelligence
community. two of them over the last 10
years saying that the Iranians do not
have a nuclear program. It was always a
joke at the CIA, Mike, when Netanyahu
would come to Washington. He would
always be invited to address Congress,
which is unusual,
but every time he comes, he's invited to
address Congress, and he would always
say that the Iranians are six months
away from a nuclear weapon. Well, you've
been saying that since 1986.
and they're still six months away from a
nuclear weapon. Well, they're not. They
never were. And and not only did the CIA
assess that they were not, but the late
Ayatollah Ali Kamayi, who was killed a
week or two ago, issued a fatwa
saying that it was it was a sin to build
a nuclear weapon and that to build a
nuclear weapon would be punishable by
death.
But we just took Netanyahu at his at his
word.
>> Well,
in July when we did bomb Iran at
Netanyahu's request, you'll recall that
the president said that the Iranian
nuclear program had been obliterated.
His word, it had been obliterated. It no
longer exists. And then from July until
now, oh my god, they're six months away
from a nuclear weapon and we have to go
in now and wage full-scale war. I was in
the Gulf a week ago and I was in the
Gulf three weeks before that in Kuwait,
Abu Dhabi, Dubai, and Doha. And I've
I've spent a good bit of my adult life
in the Persian Gulf uh serving in the in
the CIA. I love it there. And I have
wonderful close abiding relations with
all of the the various royal families
there and everywhere.
>> I got to just stop you for one minute,
John. One second. We were probably in
Dubai at the same time because I was
there just a few weeks ago.
>> I was there for two weeks and I met with
one of the the shakes and uh I got a lot
of friends in there also. So yeah, we
got out and then all heck broke loose as
they say. But uh a few days, just a few
days later,
>> but I I think you're going to agree with
me. They were all worried.
>> They were all worried because when
George W. Bush wanted to make war
against Iraq.
American diplomats went out all over the
world to make the case. The president
crisscrossed the country to win over the
American people. And this time, nothing.
Nobody went out to the Gulf to say,
"Listen, we've got a serious problem
about the Iranians. we're going to just
finish them off for once and for all.
Nobody ever had that conversation. And
so they're asking me like I'm an
insider, which I'm not. What do you
think he's going to do? I I I told I
told a senior royal in the United Arab
Emirates um I said I've been watching
this for a long time and it's my
experience that the United States would
not send two aircraft carrier strike
forces, two aircraft carrier battle
groups with 12 associated ships each
unless they meant to do serious damage.
I said I think I think we're going to
attack them.
>> Yeah.
>> Well, John, let me ask you this now.
jumping back and forth and I didn't want
to get off the Epstein matter because
there's more. But now I have to ask this
question. So Netanyahu comes now, tells
Trump, "We're going to use nuclear
weapons,
connect Epstein to Msad. Is it possible
too that they have more information and
maybe Trump does have a problem with
Epstein or there is things that he's
trying to cover up there and so maybe
there is a connection there?" There's
there certainly could be. See see this
Mike? This this is exactly what's wrong
with a lack of transparency.
>> All right, my friends. Listen up. I've
got some important news. I would say you
know my private platform, the Frenzy's
family. It's over on school. We just now
lowered it to 10 bucks a month. We
dropped it from 20 for a limited time
only because this year 2026, we're
plugging in some integral accessible
streetfilled wisdom that you never heard
of before. inside this platform. I'm
sharing very exclusive, never-beforeseen
courses. I flat out cannot put them on
YouTube. They're too real. They're too
raw. They're too deep. And if you're not
interested in learning something, you're
not going to pay attention to it. So
that's where we talk strategy, life,
faith, business, all from the
perspective of a guy who's been in the
life and now is out of the life. Our
flagship course, The Modern Prince, my
annotated breakdown of Makaveli's The
Prince, is up right now. And I'm telling
you, this is life-changing stuff for
anyone who wants to understand power,
influence, and how the game is really
played. And we're just getting started.
In the very near future, and I mean very
near future, my newest book, A Man's
Man, and my entire ministry acronyms are
all getting plugged into the school
family platform. If you want to grow as
a man, if you want to be a leader, and
if you want to grow in your faith, this
is where you need to be. So, don't wait.
Scan the QR code on the screen or go to
michaelfrances.com/family
and jump in for only 10 bucks a month.
Where you going to get a deal like this?
I'll see you on the inside because I'm
ready to share, you know, a lifetime's
worth of knowledge and wisdom and
experience with every one of you. Right?
If if you're if you're truly
transparent, just release the documents.
Just put it all out there. Let the cards
fall where they may.
By not releasing the documents, that
gives rise to conspiracies. Now, the
conspiracies may be true. Just because
they're conspiracies doesn't mean
they're not true. But it it dogs you. It
eats away at, you know, trust in your
administration and it leads people to
think that, you know what, they may have
something on him. Maybe that's why he
won't release the documents. And and
I'll add one thing. The vote on Capitol
Hill to release the documents
in the House of Representatives was 419
to1. In the Senate, it was 99 to nothing
and then the president signed it. Okay?
So, it is law. You can't just decide,
well, I don't like that law, so I'm not
doing that. That's contempt of Congress,
which can be a felony, and the attorney
general is in contempt of Congress. When
she went on national television and
said, "All right, I'm not releasing any
more documents. That's it. No more." You
can't do that. You can't say that. But
the calculation is this. The calculation
is she knows she can't do that, but
she's going to make the other side sue
her. And then it's going to go to the
federal district court and they'll lose.
And then it'll go to the circuit court
of appeals and they'll lose. And then
it'll go to the to the Supreme Court and
they may lose, but by then they're all
out of office because it took five years
to get there.
>> Yeah.
>> And I think that's what they're counting
on.
So even though that it's a law to
release them, it's still up to the
Department of Justice to see what's
redacted and what's not redacted, right?
>> Yeah. And that's another important
point.
So on the CIA side, we we had to redact
documents all the time because you've
got a mandatory declassification law
after 30 years and you also have the
Freedom of Information Act. So all of us
all of us at any given time would be
going through documents and saying,
"Okay, I'm going to black out this." And
then you write in the margin 4 HUM or
HUM4-82
or HUM1-93
or whatever which means sources and
methods, liaison relationships,
whatever. So I can't if you file a
Freedom of Information Act request about
something, I'm going to have to respond
to it, but I can't say, "Well, we got
this information from the Canadian
Intelligence Service." That's
classified, so I have to black that out.
Well, they're just blacking out like
random,
you know. Okay, I understand you want to
black out the names of the victims. God
bless. That that's that's an important
good thing to do,
>> but you can't black out the names of the
perpetrators,
>> right? These are the people that are
being invested for having committed
crimes.
>> And if you're going to black out the
email addresses, I understand that it's
a privacy issue,
>> but you don't also black out the name of
the person either sending or receiving
the emails. It's like they they stood on
the street corner and and yelled out to
a bunch of teenagers, "Hey, you guys
want a job for a couple of days? Come on
in here, grab a Sharpie, and we want you
to black stuff out." because these
people at the Justice Department didn't
know what in the world they were doing.
>> Gosh.
>> Yeah. I have to ask you, you just said
something. I want to make sure I got it
right. That there is a after 30 years
it's mandatory that uh classified
documents are released.
>> Okay. The question
>> and that's a law that like virtually
nobody knows.
>> I was going to say what about the
Kennedy assassination? We still have all
those classified documents.
>> Exactly.
>> And so by law, they should be
unclassified.
>> In fact,
>> John, I have a theory. I I have a theory
I want to share with you on that.
>> My entire life, my entire adult life,
from 1963 when the assassination
happened until the time I left my former
life, I was told there's no question
about it that we mob was involved in
that assassination through Jack Ruby.
that I don't know what government agency
came to us, but I heard this
consistently from the right people,
including my dad. I don't know what
government agency came to us, but Jack
Ruby was 100% associated with our with
us, 100%. And that's documented. From
what I understand, the commission came
back and said he had no affiliation,
which was an out and out lie. It was
just totally a lie. He was associated
with New Orleans, you know, with Chicago
and even in Dallas. That's how he got a
straight. It was 100%.
And and yet they're saying it never
happened. So I believed I always said
that one of the reasons might be more
reasons that they don't want to release
these classified documents because the
government doesn't ever want to say that
a sitting president was able to be
assassinated by people with the mob. And
that's been my position knowing what I
know. What What do you have to say? I
know we're jumping around, but this is
so interesting. I have to tell you
>> I have a couple of things to to say
about this. Um,
when I got out of prison, I struck up a
friendship with Oliver Stone.
>> He bought the uh he bought the rights to
my
>> he bought the rights to one chapter of
my first book and we we sold a show idea
together to the History Channel that
they never made.
>> But we became friendly and remained
friendly.
>> And he put me on the spot one day. I was
in his office and he said to me, "You're
not one of those you're not one of those
guys that doesn't believe that the CIA
killed Kennedy, are you?" And I said,
"You know, I think there were probably
elements of the CIA that were involved
in killing Kennedy, but in terms of
being a CIA operation to kill Kennedy,
no, I've never believed that." He said,
"You're so full of shit." And I said,
"No, no. I I genuinely I don't I don't
believe that the CIA killed Kennedy."
And he said, "Who do you think killed
Kennedy?" I said, "It was probably um
George Ganes who was kind of a rogue CIA
officer stationed in Miami. He was very
close to the Cubans." And I think that
we probably should take a closer look at
him. But I said at the same time, I
don't think we've really gotten to the
bottom of of where the mob was on all
this. And I said, you know, we we hear
these stories about Carlos Marcelo. We
we hear stories about Santo Trafocante
and the things that they said and the
immediate aftermath, like we finally got
him, you know, and and then the ties
between Chicago and Jack Ruby.
>> I said, I just don't think that's ever
been fully investigated.
He was he he got genuinely angry with me
that I didn't just agree with him. Yes,
the CIA killed Kennedy. Well, I later
struck up a a friendly acquaintance, not
we're not friends friends, but a
friendly acquaintship with Bobby Kennedy
Jr. and he and I started talking about
this one time and he said he said
something that I I told him in response.
I said, "This is historical. You should
write this down because I think the
American people need to hear your
recollections." He said on the day that
his uncle was killed, November 22nd,
1963, his mom picked him up at school
early, it was like 2:30, it was minutes
after after the assassination.
And they drove back to their home in
Mlan, Virginia. It was called Hickory
Hill. It was a glorious, you know, 40
acre spread with a mansion on the top of
the hill. And
when they pulled into the driveway, his
dad was standing there talking to John
McCone. John McCone was the director of
the CIA. The Kennedys and the MCONE were
very very close. They were they were
both devoutly Catholic. And then six
months earlier, Mrs. McCon died of
breast cancer. And the Kennedys were
genuinely worried that John McCoen might
do something to harm himself. And so
they had him over to dinner seven nights
a week just to keep an eye on him. And
then after dinner, he and Bobby Kennedy
senior would go swimming together. So
Bobby Jr. and his mom pull into the
driveway. He gets out of the car. He's
walking past his dad and he's looking at
his dad and he hears his dad say to
Mone, "Tell me your people didn't do
this." And McCone says,"I don't know who
did it."
>> He didn't say, "Wow,
>> of course my people didn't do it." Why
would you even ask such a thing like
that? He said, "I don't know who did
it." So he said, he always believed it
was the CIA.
I always believed it was elements of the
CIA. But this is I'm coming up to my
most important point. So I have a friend
who
is close to the president
and
I said to him at the time that the
documents were released what about a
year ago I said thank God that the
president finally released the remaining
documents and he said no he didn't. I
said yeah he did he was compelled by
law. Congress passed a law twice
demanding compelling the president to
release all documents related to the
Kennedy assassination.
He said, "There are 10,000 documents
that are never going to be released."
And I said, "Why?"
And he said, "Because every single one
of them points directly at Israel."
And I said, "Oh man, that's that's not
one that I was thinking of."
He says that the Israelis were so angry
that A John Kennedy wouldn't give them
nuclear technology,
but more importantly B he was actively
trying to disrupt the Israelis from
acquiring nuclear technology and they
decided they had to take him out.
>> Crazy, isn't it?
>> This this is this is fascinating, John.
Why is it that Israel seems to have this
much say over the American government? I
mean, I I don't get it. I mean,
>> yeah, I I don't either.
>> I mean, they're a small little country.
>> Yeah.
>> I know they're our only Well, not maybe
not only, but they're are major ally in
the in the Middle East, but why do they
have this kind of power and control? Is
it I don't know. I I I don't get it. The
Israelis genuinely believe that they are
alone in the world.
They know that we're close, but they're
afraid that we might not be so close
tomorrow. And so, they genuinely believe
that it is them against the world. And
if they are not among the strongest
powers in the world, they're going to
end up floating in the Mediterranean.
And so
they made a strategic decision in the
middle 1950s that they were going to
have as much of an impact in American
elections as they possibly could. Apac,
the American Israel Public Affairs
Committee was created in the 1950s as a
domestic lobbying organization
supporting Israeli uh foreign policy
goals. Every country has lobbyists in in
Washington. There's nothing unusual
about that. What's unusual about it
though? Well, there are several things.
Number one, APEC is the only one of
these organizations that does not have
to register as a foreign agent. Why?
I don't know why. They're clearly
working on behalf of Israel, but they
pretend that they're not, and so they
don't have to register as foreign
agents. More importantly,
they really started focusing on
fundraising for American elections in
the late 1960s. And then they were
successful in getting President Nixon in
to guarantee Israeli national security.
We had never said that before. Beginning
with Harry Truman. You know, Harry
Truman said that his role in the
creation of the state of Israel made him
quote a damn fool. That he was a damn
fool for creating that country. and he
said it was the biggest regret of his
presidency because it spun out of
control almost immediately. So they they
created Apac in the 50s. They convince
Nixon to to guarantee their national
security in 69 and then they start going
from, you know, being able to raise a
couple of million bucks, 5 million, 10
million to raising hundreds and hundreds
of millions of dollars that would allow
them to to be competitive in literally
every political race in America. And
I'll tell you a funny thing, Mike. I
shouldn't smile because it's actually
not funny. So, a buddy of mine is a uh
he's one of these like civic leaders in
Texas. And so,
he's friendly with a state senator in
Austin. And the state senator called
him, this is about a month ago, and
said, "Hey, listen. I'm going to propose
a resolution to make a day named after
you, like the the the Bill Smith Day."
And he said, "They do about 140 of these
a year. whoever's, you know, you're the
head of the Social Security Commission
or whatever, they're going to make a
Mike Franzy's day and and you get a big
certificate with the gold seal and the
governor signs it and everything. He
said it's all proforma. Couple of weeks
later, he calls back and he says, "Hey,
listen. That uh that Bill Smith day,
that's not going to happen." And my
buddy said, "Why?"
He said, "Apac killed it." And I said,
"Apac
in the state legislature in Texas."
It turns out that they have lobbyists in
all 50 state legislatores. It's not just
the House and the Senate here in
Washington. He told me they're even
involved in local races, not just the
New York mayoral race. They're involved
in races for mayor all over the country
and for city council all over the
country because they want to make the
United States a 100% pro-Zionist country
and uh and they're succeeding.
Well, John, I got to ask you this and uh
it may seem that we're bouncing around,
but the Israeli connection makes it very
interesting. Charlie Kirk.
>> Charlie Kirk. everybody. Well, there's a
lot of people out there that believe
that Israel was behind his
assassination.
What do you have to say about that? I
mean, I was I always said no, but I'm
learning something here right now. I
mean, you know, I I always said no, too,
but
but you know, there are so many people
out there, Mike, who I respect,
people far more important than than I
could ever be,
who say, "Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
There's enough there that we should at
least investigate it. We should at least
look at it. I don't think that it was,
you know, the Egyptian Air Force like
Candace Owen says that the Egyptian Air
Force killed him. But uh but you know,
Charlie was Charlie was kind of cutting
an independent path
and there are a lot of there are a lot
of interests out there that don't want
people to take independent paths. And so
at the very least, I think we owe it
well certainly to Charlie's family and
more broadly to the American people to
investigate this thing.
Well, there again, if if if
there is an Israeli connection to Trump
like that, um, you know, he would be the
one that would kill any kind of an
investigation that would point in any
way towards Israel. It would seem. I
think that was, you know, something we
can consider.
>> Man, this is such a a a deeply woven web
>> of information. I I want to go back to
uh to Epstein for a moment.
>> I have always maintained that I spent
seven months in MDC. Out of my 29 months
in solitary, seven months was in MDC.
I find it very, very tough to believe
that he could have committed suicide
based upon my experience there. Add to
that what I've read and I think that's I
think it's been verified that it took
the FBI who are right across the street
from MDC
7 hours before they came over to
investigate the fact that their main
inmate in that jail was committed
suicide.
>> Yeah.
>> And I've maintained this. There's no way
he could have committed suicide. So my
theory behind it was that he probably
said to whoever, "Hey, I got dirt on
every one of you. you get me out of this
like you got me out of this earlier or
some heads are going to fly. I'm going
to reveal everything. And at that point,
they took him out and now it makes even
more sense because of what you said with
this kill list.
>> Yeah.
>> They just took him out. Um
>> Absolutely.
>> What do we need this for?
>> Absolutely plausible. Yeah.
>> You know, I
>> I wasn't at MDC. I was at FCI Lorettto
in Pennsylvania. But if my experience
was
>> was indicative of the the broader um
Bureau of Prisons, and I think you'll
agree with me, number one, the guards
are morons.
They're lazy. They're in the guard booth
either sound asleep or on the phone with
their girlfriends or looking at porn on
the computer. They're supposed to walk
around whatever it is every 15 minutes,
every eight minutes when there's
somebody on suicide watch. I never saw
those guys. They walk into the booth for
their eight hour shift and they walk out
eight hours later for the very first
time. Number two, the cameras never
work. Now,
they may have counted on the cameras
never working. So, that may have been
part of the plan. I was I was a janitor
in the chapel, Mike, and every time
there was a religious service being
planned, I had to go in there and shoe
all the guys who were having sex out of
the chapel.
>> So why were there guys having sex in the
chapel? Because the cameras didn't work.
The cameras never worked. Now, with that
said, this is MDC. It's not some low
security, you know, rural prison in
Pennsylvania. These are these are very
tough people, very bad people in many
cases. And, you know, I I guess I wanted
to believe that he had committed
suicide, but then when Dr. Boden, you
know, Dr. Bodton, the famous famous uh
>> forensic uh Yeah.
>> when he said,
>> he's one guy I I I really trust him,
John. you know, I've watched him and and
you know, going way way back and I trust
his,
>> you know, his analysis or his
investigation on this.
>> And when he said that this was not a
suicide, then I thought, okay, well, I'm
with Dr. Boden.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. It's not only that, John, if
Epstein had all of this information, and
he obviously did, why would he want to
commit suicide? I mean, his brother said
it didn't make sense.
>> It doesn't make sense.
It doesn't make sense, you know, and let
me tell you an associated story. Um, I
was in a low security prison and as you
know, almost all the pedophiles in the
in the federal prison system are in low
security prisons. Maximums and mediums
are too dangerous for them. Minimums,
they'll just run away and go molest
another child. So, they're all in the
lows. Right.
>> There was a there was a very prominent
Philadelphia attorney, Harvard Law
School, uh, mergers and acquisitions uh,
lead attorney at some big mucky muck
firm in Moscow,
American firm in Moscow, but he was a
pedophile.
And so he molested this little boy 12
from when he was 12 to when he was 15.
And he got caught.
And when he came back to the United
States, he got wind that
he was being investigated. Well, not
even that he got wind. The kid filed a
civil suit against him. And so what did
he do? He ran away to Israel. Why
Israel? Because Israel doesn't extradite
Jews. They don't care what you did. You
can be a mass murderer, a serial killer.
You can be a pedophile. You can be the
most notorious pedophile in the world.
They're not extraditing you because they
don't extradite Jews. So this guy ran to
Israel.
Well, he was a great lover of the ballet
and the boy that he was molesting was
this ballet prodigy in Moscow. So what
Interpol did, it was brilliant. They
took out ads in Israeli newspapers
saying that there was going to be this
one time only
uh ballet featuring the greatest child
ballerinas
uh coming from Russia and it was for one
night only in Cyprus. Well, Cypress is a
hop, skip, and a jump from Israel. You
get there in 40 minutes.
>> And sure enough,
>> sure enough, he got on a plane. He flew
to Cypress to see this non-existent
ballet and they grabbed him in Cyprus
and extradited him to the United States
and he got 20 years. So with that said,
if I were Jeffrey Epstein
and I own my own, you know,
jets, multiple jets, I've got billions
of dollars hidden all around the world.
Why in the world would I not flee to
Israel? The only thing that I can think
of
>> Yeah. Why? Why would he stay? The only
thing I can think of is that he believed
he was safe. He believed he was safe.
And I think it's because of what you
just said that he had so much dirt on so
many important people that they wouldn't
dare come after him. And then they did.
It's it's the only thing that makes
sense, you know, really.
>> But there again, you know, was Israel if
he was with MSAD, Israel was collecting
all of this information and they would
have information from the indication
that people that were involved in this
horrible Epstein thing. They must have
dirt on so many people in the world of
of stature, of meaning, of wealth.
>> Imagine. Imagine.
>> Yeah, it has to be
>> like my guess is we can't even we can't
even imagine
what they were able to collect through
him. It has to be just staggering. I
mean, already in the UK, look what's
happening. Uh, Prince Andrew is no
longer a prince. And not only is he no
longer a prince, he he's been stripped
of his royal residence, essentially just
thrown out into the street and arrested
last week and he's going to be
prosecuted because he allegedly gave
Jeffrey Epstein classified defense
ministry documents. Why in blazes would
Jeffrey Epstein want classified UK
defense ministry documents unless he's
spying for a foreign power? uh pet Peter
Mandlesson.
>> Absolutely.
>> The the former uh British ambassador to
the United States and former minister
and member of the House of Lords and
senior member of the Labor Party. He
kept saying, "I didn't even know the
guy. I met him one time. I didn't I
didn't have his number. I had never been
to the island." And then in the latest
trunch of documents, there are pictures
of him in his underwear with a
16-year-old girl with a the picture's
taken from a hidden camera.
So now they've arrested him. Why would
they charge him with for providing
Jeffrey Epstein with classified trade
negotiation documents, British positions
on trade negotiations? What's Jeffrey
Epstein going to do with that? He
doesn't care about trade negotiations.
It was for a foreign power.
>> Exactly. Exactly. Because And he had to
have a lot of dirt in order to get that
that documentation. It's unbelievable.
>> Unbelievable what this guy was able to
do. It's just
>> So I So you would you would tend to
believe then that it was uh it was
murder and not suicide.
>> Yeah. I've It took me a little while
around to it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I've come around to to
murder. Yes.
Yeah. I don't believe that it's a body
double and he escaped and all this
stuff. I spoke to his brother a couple
of weeks ago and his brother said, "No."
He said, "I identified the body. I
accompanied the body to the crematorium.
I cremated him." So, I I believe Jeffrey
Epstein's dead, but I've I've finally
come around to the to the murder issue.
Unbelievable. All right, let let let's
jump back to uh to Iran. So if if in
fact
Trump acted because of pressure from
Netanyahu, who by the way, I have a
friend of mine, very dear friend of
mine, he's an Israeli, 35 years. He
hates Netanyahu. Hates him with a
passion. And he's Israeli.
>> Most Israelis do.
>> And you know, he's
>> Huh.
>> Most Israelis do hate him. He he's in
Bulgaria now, my friend. He wants to
come here. And I said, "Why do you hate
this guy so much?" He's I'm going to
tell you when I see I don't want to talk
about it on the phone. Israelis are
very, you know, they're very definite in
things, but uh he hates him. Hates him
with a passion. It's unbelievable. But I
I don't know why, so I can't comment on
that. But going back to the war, if in
fact that happened, my what I'm saying
right now, if Trump doesn't finish the
job, and I mean really finish the job,
his presidency is done. I mean, he's
he's finished.
>> I agree.
>> He has no choice. Now, I think if
Netanyahu did back him into this corner
and he did act, he's going to finish it.
And I don't think I don't think Israel
would let them get off the hook at this
point. They're going to they're going to
finish the job if they can.
>> Do do you think this you think it was
just you know he had to put it out there
Putin that he said he's supporting Iran
all the way and he's condemning uh what
happened you know here the war.
>> You think it's just he has to say that
it's bluster. Do you think they would
ever get involved?
I I don't the the Russians have been
very
>> The Russians have been very uh clear to
not say that Iran falls under the
Russian defense umbrella. They sell Iran
guidance systems, radars,
surfaceto-air missiles. They sell them
all that stuff, but they've never said
that they would protect Iran in the
event of hostilities. And you know, with
Trump, I I think again, I think that
Trump really believed
that
as soon as we started hitting the
Iranians and we killed not just Ayat
Kamayi, but virtually the entire uh
defense leadership, he really believed
the country would just collapse like a
house of cards. And it didn't.
And the thing, look at it this way, too.
We have to win
to win. We have to replace that
government with a pro-american,
pro- West, maybe even pro-Israel
government. The Iranians just have to
survive.
Just survival is a win for them. So, we
may have bitten off more than we could
chew here.
>> Well, I hope he didn't underestimate
them to that point. I I I I think, you
know, as a novice in this,
>> I'm thinking that right now he he's
going to kill everybody if he can. He he
wants to kill the new guy, the son that
they just installed.
>> And he's hopeful
>> that the Kurds and and the people will
start to rise up that he'll weaken,
>> you know, the present administration
enough so that when they do revolt, they
can win.
>> Yes.
>> I mean, I think that's the card he's
playing.
>> I think that's exactly right.
>> Does it sound right? Yeah, I think
that's exactly what this is. And you
know, we're we're in now to the point
where
we're we're in deeply enough that we we
can't get out. This is uh this is it. We
we've got to either see it through or
walk away. And we can't walk away
because we'll lose face. And we'll lose
face especially with our neighbor our
our friends, I should say, not our
neighbors, with our friends in the
Persian Gulf. You know, we started this.
We're going to have to finish it because
they're taking missiles. They have
people being killed. So, we we've got to
make this right.
Well, John, let me let me ask you this.
I think everybody all the foreign
nations and all our allies believe that
Iran
is the major sponsor of terrorism
throughout the world. They all know
that. They all know that the regime was
murdering their own people for 47 years.
>> Yeah. Why don't they all just get
together and say, "Let's just let's just
eliminate this threat, period. So, we'll
all contribute. NATO, whatever it is,
we'll all get and we'll get the job
done. We'll help the United States and
finish it."
>> Yeah.
>> It seems like they're coming around a
little bit at a time. But why why did
they not all just get together and say,
"Let's finish it."
>> I think for a couple of reasons. Number
one, war is incredibly expensive. We are
spending $2 billion a day bombing the
Iranians. It's crazy expensive. Number
two, and this is especially true among
our NATO allies, they don't have the
stomach for casualties that we have.
They just don't want to have to deal
with it. And number three, and this is
true of the the Germans, the Spanish,
the Portuguese, the Italians,
um
it's a violation of international law to
attack Iran. There was no clear and
present danger. There was no imminent
threat. There was no nuclear program.
And there even if they had a nuclear
program, there was no delivery system.
So because there was no threat, it's a
violation of international law to launch
an attack. Now, we don't we're not
signitories to the ICC. We don't care
if, you know, Donald Trump gets charged
with crimes against humanity. We don't
care. and the Israelis care even less,
but the Europeans care very much and
they just don't want to be part of a
major crime like that.
>> Do you think uh Saudi Arabia because
Iran is just sending missiles
everywhere, do you think at some point
they're going to get involved
offensively rather than just
defensively?
>> It's possible, but there are almost no
Saudis in the Saudi military. Uh Saudis
are too rich. They're too fat and happy.
They're They just don't have any Saudi
nationals in the Saudi military. They're
all Pakistanis.
So, there are so many people in
Pakistan, so many poor people that they
just hire Pakistanis to be members of
the Saudi military. Um, they could do
that. They could send they could send
Pakistanis over, but uh I think they
would just rather wait this out. maybe
absorb a couple of missiles if they have
to, especially in the eastern province
where the oil fields are, and then just
move on from there.
>> Wow.
>> Yeah.
>> I want I want to jump back because I
know I'm going back to Epstein, but I
have to tell you this. Bill Clinton, you
know, I'll give you a personal thing.
One night, this is years ago, this was
after his presidency. I was listening to
him on a late night talk show. And John,
I was amazed at how brilliant this guy
really is. I mean, he had such command
over every issue.
>> Yes.
>> And the way he I always liked Bill.
There's something about Bill Clinton you
just got to like. He He's likable. I
can't I can't explain it.
>> But I think he and Hillary made fools
out of the GOP in their deposition. He
he just he just handled them.
>> Yeah. I one of the things with the GOP,
you know, they have so much bluster
about them and they talk and they don't
do anything.
>> They don't do anything.
>> That's exactly right.
>> Nothing.
>> I just made a fool out of him.
>> I think that that they they played the
Republicans in these uh these
testimonies. And then Lauren Boowbert,
like how stupid could a person be?
>> After being told twice
no photography, she takes a picture of
Hillary testifying and puts it on
Instagram.
Like she just can't be a serious person.
Mike, please please dumb.
>> It was so dumb. Please forgive me, but
I've got to jump onto a business call.
Um, and I I apologize deeply.
No, John, this this was great and I hope
one day we get the opportunity to do it
again.
>> I would love it. I have so much respect
at your service. I mean it.
>> Thank you. I'm at your service.
>> Well, we will we will definitely do it.
>> I look forward to that very much.
>> You got it, my friend. Thanks.
>> So great to see you.
>> Thanks a lot, my friends. I don't know
about you, but I'm blown away by this. I
mean, he's given me food for thought
about Israel because he's tying this all
together, even with a little bit with
Charlie Kerr. Not to the degree that
people are spreading stuff out there,
but Israel does seem to be involved in a
lot of stuff. It's making me rethink
some things based upon what he said. And
this is a person with knowledge and
understanding. Was with the CIA for a
long time. I'm going to tell you
something. I'm going to be disappointed
in some people here if this does fit in
the way it seems to be fitting in and
making sense. I'm not ready to throw the
gavl down and say that's it. I still
want to continue to learn because let me
tell you something people. I don't point
fingers at people unless I know
something for sure. It's why I've been
reluctant to call people
unless I know for sure and have the
evidence because that's disgusting and I
don't want to label anybody with that
unless I have evidence. That's just me.
A lot of people throw things around.
They don't like people. They say I don't
do that. And I'd said this and I
admitted it here if you heard the
interview. I thought Clinton took the
GOP to school in the Epstein
investigation. He took him to school.
Clinton is brilliant. No question about
it. And you know what? There's something
about the guy that's very likable. All
you MAGA people or all all the people
that are on the Republican side are
going to get mad at me for that. I'm not
I'm not saying that what he I'm not
saying anything about some of the things
that he was involved in. I'm just
telling you he's a brilliant guy.
There's no question about it. Bill
Clinton is smart. And even Hillary, she
held herself very well in that. And and
some of the things that she was asked, I
didn't agree with. I didn't approve of
it in my mind. What do you got to go
that low for really? I don't think they
treated her fairly. That's my opinion.
And you know that I'm a conservative in
many ways, in many of my views. But I
tell it like it is, people. That's what
you're going to get from me. I tell it
like it is. And if I'm wrong and I find
out I'm wrong, I'm going to admit it
later on. That's the bottom line. So
anyway, unbelievable what he had to say.
What he had to say about I didn't
realize this. It's a law that after 30
years you must release classified
documents and it's been 62 years and
they haven't released the Kennedy
documents. I told you why. Because
there's a lot more to it and it'll show
the mob's involvement because the
Warrant Commission lied about Jack
Ruby's involvement with the mob.
Absolutely lied.
So much here. This government covers up
so much, not only the current
government, but our government, period.
That's why I wrote the book, Mafia
Democracy, because I've seen it and I've
known it and I've experienced it. We're
never going to get the truth, no matter
what. No matter who's in office, no ma
We're never going to get the truth about
things that are really important. Not
Epstein, not this war in Iran. We're
never going to get the truth. Kennedy,
none of that. Face the facts. Don't
blame any particular guy. Yeah, they're
all in the same boat when it comes to
that. All right? That's just the system.
It's the way it is. Is it right? No. Am
I covering for anybody? No. Am I making
excuses? No. I'm telling you, that's
just the way it is. So, take it. But
John, thank you so much for for uh
sitting down with me. I mean, this this
was great and explosive and you got me
thinking to a point where I'm going to
really study this and do some more
research. I'd love to have him back on.
There's so many other things I want to
talk to him about and we will have him
back on. My friends, how do I leave you
same way? Never going to change. Be
safe. Please, we got these terrorist
cells in this country now. Who knows
when we're going to have another, you
know, incident. I hope never. But come
on, be careful when you're out in
public. Just be careful, people. Please
be safe. be healthy. I don't have to go
into that. You know what the deal is on
that. And yes, God bless each and every
one of you, your family, your friends,
your neighborhood, your communities, and
more than ever, God bless America, that
we come out of this thing, all of these
different issues, especially this war in
Iran. Let's hope that we come out of
this thing the right way for everybody
involved, not so much the the uh the bad
Iranian administration, but the Iranian
people. Okay? And people, let me just
put this out there right now for all you
ridiculous, stupid comments. You know, I
don't want to see any Palestinian you,
you know, uh, people being killed. I
don't want to see kids, women, children.
I don't care who they are, what they
are, where they are. I don't want to see
it. So, when I say I care about the
Iranian people, don't right away bring
about the Palestinian people. Of course,
I don't like that. And I've said it. We
don't want to see any innocent people
murdered. So, stop with the stupid
comments. You're talking about Iranians,
but you haven't said anything about, you
know, the uh the killings in Palestine.
Yes, I have. I don't want to see any
innocent people die anywhere. Period.
End of story. So, let's pray. Let's pray
to God that he he gets some kind of, you
know, peace in this world. Never going
to happen. But maybe to a degree where
at least people are surviving in the
places where they're being, you know,
murdered and just not treated fairly.
Even Christians being martyed in in
places all over the world. And you know,
there are there are a lot of Christians
in Iran. A lot of them. They're
undercover because they get killed for
it. The same way gays get killed for it.
The same way women get and murdered. All
right. All you people that are wanting
this administration in there, same way.
So, let's just pray that God shines a
light on all of us. See you next time,
my friends. Stay tuned.